Guide to the Sports Information Office Records, 1932-ongoing UA.13.02.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- UA2013-0034, 1927-2015
  - Wrestling: Certificates for Individuals, circa 1980-1989; 26 folders (Box UA2013-0034.12)
  - Wrestling: Stats and Schedule, 1986-1989 (Box UA2013-0034.12)
  - Wrestling: Photos, circa 1973-2007 (Box UA2013-0034.12)
  - Wrestling: West Point, 1963-1964 (Box UA2013-0034.12)
  - Wrestling: Photos, 1966-1967 (Box UA2013-0034.12)
  - Wrestling: Photos, 1967-1968 (Box UA2013-0034.12)
  - Wrestling: Photos, 1968-1969 (Box UA2013-0034.12)
  - Wrestling: Photos, 1969-1970 (Box UA2013-0034.12)
  - Wrestling: Photos, 1970-1971 (Box UA2013-0034.12)
  - Wrestling: Photos, 1971-1972 (Box UA2013-0034.12)
  - Wrestling: Photos, 1972-1973 (Box UA2013-0034.12)
  - Wrestling: Photos, 1975-1976 (Box UA2013-0034.12)
  - Wrestling: Photos, 1976-1977 (Box UA2013-0034.12)
  - Wrestling: Photos, 1977-1978 (Box UA2013-0034.12)
  - Wrestling: Photos, 1978-1979 (Box UA2013-0034.12)
  - Wrestling: Photos, 1979-1980 (Box UA2013-0034.12)
  - Wrestling: Materials, circa 1980-1989 (Box UA2013-0034.12)
  - Wrestling: Stats, circa 1980-1989 (Box UA2013-0034.12)
  - Wrestling: Brackets, 1988-1989 (Box UA2013-0034.12)
  - Wrestling: Brackets, 1987-1988 (Box UA2013-0034.12)
  - Wrestling: Brackets, circa 1980-1989 (Box UA2013-0034.12)
  - Wrestling: Materials, circa 1980-1989 (Box UA2013-0034.12)
  - Wrestling: Weight Confirmation and Scorebook, 2007-2008 (Box UA2013-0034.12)
  - Wrestling: Stats and Schedule, 1981-1997 (Box UA2013-0034.12)
  - Wrestling: Championship Programs, circa 1980-1989 (Box UA2013-0034.12)
  - Wrestling: Programs; Calendar, 1980-1981; 2004-2005 (Box UA2013-0034.12)
  - Wrestling: Articles, 1988-1989 (Box UA2013-0034.12)
  - Wrestling: Clippings, circa 1980-1989; 2 folders (Box UA2013-0034.12)
  - Wrestling: Newspaper Clips, 1995-1996 (Box UA2013-0034.12)
  - Wrestling: Photos, circa 1980-1989 (Box UA2013-0034.12)
  - Wrestling: Clippings, circa 1980-1989; 2 folders (Box UA2013-0034.12)
  - Wrestling: NCAA/ACC Publications, circa 1980-1989; 2 folders (Box UA2013-0034.13)
  - Wrestling: Tournament Info, circa 1980-1989 (Box UA2013-0034.13)
  - Wrestling: NCAA Championship, 1983 (Box UA2013-0034.13)
  - Wrestling: Photos and Clippings, 1974-1975 (Box UA2013-0034.13)
  - Wrestling: NCAA Publications, circa 1980-1989 (Box UA2013-0034.13)
  - Wrestling: Duke Publications, circa 1980-1989 (Box UA2013-0034.13)
  - Wrestling: Clippings, circa 1980-1989 (Box UA2013-0034.13)
  - Wrestling: Workouts, 1971-1974; 3 folders (Box UA2013-0034.13)
  - Wrestling: ACC Material, circa 1980-1989 (Box UA2013-0034.13)
  - Wrestling: NCAA Championship, 1980 (Box UA2013-0034.13)
  - Wrestling: Amateur Wrestling News, 1980-1985 (Box UA2013-0034.13)
  - Wrestling: Stats and Schedules, 1985-1987 (Box UA2013-0034.13)
  - Wrestling: Stats and Schedules, 1996-1997 (Box UA2013-0034.13)
  - Wrestling: ACC Results, 1991 (Box UA2013-0034.13)
  - Wrestling: ACC, 1992 (Box UA2013-0034.13)
  - Wrestling: Stats, circa 1990-2006 (Box UA2013-0034.13)
  - Wrestling: Brackets, circa 1990-2006 (Box UA2013-0034.13)
  - Wrestling: Calendar, 2005-2006 (Box UA2013-0034.13)
  - Wrestling: Varsity and Player Information, circa 1990-2006 (Box UA2013-0034.13)
  - Wrestling: Varsity Letters, circa 1990-2006; 4 folders (Box UA2013-0034.13)
  - Wrestling: Certificates for Individuals, circa 1990-2006 (Box UA2013-0034.13)
  - Wrestling: Clippings, 1982-1983 (Box UA2013-0034.13)
  - Wrestling: Varsity and Certificates, circa 1980-1990 (Box UA2013-0034.13)
  - Wrestling: Varsity Results, 1927-1983 (Box UA2013-0034.13)
  - Wrestling: Certificates, circa 1980-1990 (Box UA2013-0034.13)
  - Wrestling: Photos, 1984-1996; 13 folders (Box UA2013-0034.13)
  - Wrestling: Photos, circa 1980-1990 (Box UA2013-0034.13)
  - Wrestling: NCAA/ACC Publications, circa 1980-1990 (Box UA2013-0034.13)
  - Wrestling: Information Cards, circa 1980-1990 (Box UA2013-0034.13)
  - Wrestling: Clippings, circa 1980-1990 (Box UA2013-0034.14)
  - Wrestling: Keith Paulik, Dumfries, VA, circa 1980-1990 (Box UA2013-0034.14)
  - Wrestling: Drew Muzslay, Ocean City, NJ, circa 1980-1990 (Box UA2013-0034.14)
  - Wrestling: Dan Lilley, Alexandria, NJ, circa 1980-1990 (Box UA2013-0034.14)
  - Wrestling: John Kays, Piscataway, NJ, circa 1980-1990 (Box UA2013-0034.14)
  - Wrestling: Season Clippings, 1990-1991 (Box UA2013-0034.14)
  - Wrestling: Report, circa 1980-1990 (Box UA2013-0034.14)
  - Wrestling: NCAA News Clips, 1988 (Box UA2013-0034.14)
  - Wrestling: Clippings, circa 1980-1990 (Box UA2013-0034.14)
  - Wrestling: NCAA, 1987 (Box UA2013-0034.14)
  - Wrestling: Stats Booklet, circa 1980-1990 (Box UA2013-0034.14)
  - Wrestling: Articles Newspaper, circa 1980-1990 (Box UA2013-0034.14)
  - Wrestling:Alumni, circa 1980-1990 (Box UA2013-0034.14)
  - Wrestling: Letter Winners, circa 1980-1990 (Box UA2013-0034.14)
  - Wrestling: Awards Outstanding Wrestler, circa 1980-1990 (Box UA2013-0034.14)
  - Wrestling: Address List and Summer Letters, circa 1980-1990 (Box UA2013-0034.14)
  - Wrestling: Posters, circa 1980-1990 (Box UA2013-0034.14)
  - Wrestling: Poster (Rolled), 1999-2000 (Box UA2013-0034.14)
  - Football: Photos, circa 1980-2010 (Box UA2013-0034.15)
  - Wrestling: Certificates and Awards, circa 1990-2000 (Box UA2013-0034.15)
  - Wrestling: Clippings, circa 1990-2000 (Box UA2013-0034.15)
  - Wrestling: Photos, 1990-1991 (Box UA2013-0034.15)
  - Wrestling: Stats, Articles, Brackets, 2001-2002 (Box UA2013-0034.15)
  - Wrestling: Stats, Articles, Brackets, 1998-1999 (Box UA2013-0034.15)
  - Wrestling: Stats, Articles, Brackets, 1997-1998 (Box UA2013-0034.15)
  - Wrestling: Stats, Articles, Brackets, 1996-1997 (Box UA2013-0034.15)
  - Wrestling: Stats and Schedules, 1995-1996 (Box UA2013-0034.15)
  - Wrestling: Stats and Schedules, 1994-1995 (Box UA2013-0034.15)
  - Wrestling: Stats, Articles, Brackets, 1999-2000 (Box UA2013-0034.15)
  - Wrestling: Stats, Articles, Brackets, 2002-2003 (Box UA2013-0034.15)
  - Wrestling: Program Materials, 1970s; 4 folders (Box UA2013-0034.15)
  - Wrestling: Program Materials, 1980s (Box UA2013-0034.15)
  - Wrestling: Tournament Results, 2003-2004 (Box UA2013-0034.15)
  - Wrestling: Notebooks, circa 2003-2007; 2 Volumes (Box UA2013-0034.15)
  - Wrestling: Calendar, 2006-2007 (Box UA2013-0034.15)
  - Wrestling: Scorebooks, 1978-1984 (Box UA2013-0034.15)
  - Wrestling: Scorebooks, 1963-2004 (Box UA2013-0034.16)
    Includes thirty-five scorebooks.
  - Wrestling: Stats and Schedules, 1971-1978 (Box UA2013-0034.16)
  - Wrestling: Clippings, circa 1970-1990 (Box UA2013-0034.16)
  - Wrestling: Statistics, circa 1970-1990 (Box UA2013-0034.16)
  - Football: Assorted Media Guides and Yearbooks, 1985-1998 (Box UA2013-0034.17)
  - Swimming and Diving: Senior Class Program, 2000-2007 (Box UA2013-0034.17)
  - Women's Tennis: Programs, 2004-2008 (Box UA2013-0034.17)
  - Track & Field: Program Info, 2008; 3 folders (Box UA2013-0034.17)
  - Cross Country: Program Info, 2007 (Box UA2013-0034.17)
  - Wrestling: Media Guides, 1997-2003 (Box UA2013-0034.17)
  - Wrestling: Media Guides, 1975-1997 (Box UA2013-0034.17)
  - Wrestling: Photos, 1979; 2006 (Box UA2013-0034.17)
  - Football: Yearbook, 1999-2007 (Box UA2013-0034.18)
  - Women's Basketball: Photos, circa 1980-1990; 2 folders (Box UA2013-0034.18)
  - Blue Devil Weekly - Bound, 2002-2006 (Box UA2013-0034.19)
  - Women's Basketball: Photos, 1999; 4 folders (Box UA2013-0034.20)
  - Women's Basketball: Contact Sheets and Negatives, circa 1990-2013; 2 folders (Box UA2013-0034.20)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Hampton, NCAA Tournament, 2011-03-18 (Box UA2013-0034.20)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Michigan, NCAA Tournament, 2011-03-20 (Box UA2013-0034.20)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Arizona, NCAA Tournament, 2011-03-24 (Box UA2013-0034.20)
  - Men and Women Cross Country: Releases, 2002 (Box UA2013-0034.21)
  - Men and Women Cross Country: ACC Releases, 2002 (Box UA2013-0034.21)
  - Football: Yearbook, 1999-2001 (Box UA2013-0034.21)
  - Duke Basketball: An Illustrated History by Bill Brill, 2012; 10 items (Box UA2013-0034.21)
    Includes an autographed copy.
  - Student Athlete Questionnaires and Clippings, circa 2002-2010 (Box UA2013-0034.21)
  - ACC Certificates, circa 2002-2010 (Box UA2013-0034.21)
  - Track and Field & Cross Country: Programs, 2005-2010 (Box UA2013-0034.21)
  - Swimming and Diving: Senior Class Program, 2007-2008 (Box UA2013-0034.21)
  - Men's Lacrosse: Program, 2007 (Box UA2013-0034.21)
  - Assorted Clippings and Statistics, circa 1995-2007 (Box UA2013-0034.21)
    Includes digital disks.
  - Men's Basketball: Statistics, 1995; 1999 (Box UA2013-0034.22)
  - Men's Basketball: Jason Williams Photos, 1991-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.22)
  - Men's Basketball: The Chronicle, 2008-03-06 (Box UA2013-0034.22)
  - Assorted Clippings, circa 1980-2008 (Box UA2013-0034.22)
  - Men's Basketball: Schedules and Scores, 1980-2002 (Box UA2013-0034.22)
  - Women's Golf: Aazam-Zanganeh, Niloufar, circa 2000-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.22)
  - Men's Basketball: Scores and Statistics, 1986-1987 (Box UA2013-0034.22)
  - Men's Basketball: NCAA Box Scores, 1992-1993 (Box UA2013-0034.22)
  - Men's Basketball: NCAA Box Scores, 1989-1990 (Box UA2013-0034.22)
  - Men's Basketball: Sports Illustrated; NCAA Box Scores, 2005; 1995 (Box UA2013-0034.22)
  - Men's Soccer: Clipping & Men's Lacrosse: Score, 2007; 1986 (Box UA2013-0034.22)
  - Assorted Player Photos, circa 1980-2008 (Box UA2013-0034.22)
  - Men's Lacrosse: Steve Ahrens, circa 1990-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.22)
  - Men's Lacrosse: Will Aherne, circa 1990-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.22)
  - Men's Lacrosse: David Aherne, circa 1990-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.22)
  - Arten-Anderson, Elizabeth Margaret - Academic Coordinator, circa 1990-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.22)
  - Men's Soccer: Matt Ahumada, circa 1990-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.22)
  - Men's Baseball: Soo Kyo Ahn, circa 1990-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.22)
  - Assorted Clippings, circa 1990-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.22)
  - Football: Photos and Clippings, circa 1990-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.23)
    Many photos relate to Zaid Abdul-Aleem.
  - Baseball: Schedule, 2000 (Box UA2013-0034.23)
  - Men and Women's Tennis: Programs and Photos, 2001; 2006-2007 (Box UA2013-0034.23)
  - Assorted Sports Material: Golf, Men's Lacrosse, Men's Soccer, circa 1990-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.23)
  - Men's Basketball: Clippings, Box Scores, Photos, Media Guides, circa 1990-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.23)
  - Men's Track: Photos, Media Guides, Contact Sheets, 1991 (Box UA2013-0034.23)
  - Women's Rowing: Burton, Erin, circa 1990-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.23)
  - Brodie, H. Keith H., circa 1990-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.23)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. North Carolina, 2013-03-09 (Box UA2013-0034.23)
  - Men's Basketball: ACC Tournament: Duke vs. Maryland, 2013-03-15 (Box UA2013-0034.23)
  - Men's Basketball: NCAA Tournament: Duke vs. Albany, 2013-03-22 (Box UA2013-0034.23)
  - Men's Basketball: NCAA Tournament: Duke vs. Creighton, 2013-03-24 (Box UA2013-0034.23)
  - Men's Basketball: NCAA Tournament: Duke vs. Michigan State, 2013-03-29 (Box UA2013-0034.23)
  - Men's Basketball: NCAA Tournament: Duke vs. Louisville, 2013-03-31 (Box UA2013-0034.23)
  - Women's Swimming and Diving: Clippings, 2013 (Box UA2013-0034.23)
  - Swimming and Diving: Meet Results, 2012-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.23)
  - Men's Basketball: Countdown to Craziness, 2012-10-19 (Box UA2013-0034.24)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Western Washington, 2012-10-27 (Box UA2013-0034.24)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Winston-Salem State, 2012-11-01 (Box UA2013-0034.24)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Georgia State, 2012-11-09 (Box UA2013-0034.24)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Kentucky, 2012-11-13 (Box UA2013-0034.24)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Florida Gulf Coast, 2012-11-18 (Box UA2013-0034.24)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Minnesota (Battle 4 Atlantis), 2012-11-22 (Box UA2013-0034.24)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. VCU (Battle 4 Atlantis), 2012-11-23 (Box UA2013-0034.24)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Louisville (Battle 4 Atlantis), 2012-11-24 (Box UA2013-0034.24)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Ohio State, 2012-11-28 (Box UA2013-0034.24)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Delaware, 2012-12-01 (Box UA2013-0034.24)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Temple, 2012-12-08 (Box UA2013-0034.24)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Cornell, 2012-12-19 (Box UA2013-0034.24)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Elon, 2012-12-20 (Box UA2013-0034.24)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Santa Clara, 2012-12-29 (Box UA2013-0034.24)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Davidson, 2013-01-02 (Box UA2013-0034.24)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Wake Forest, 2013-01-05 (Box UA2013-0034.24)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Clemson, 2013-01-08 (Box UA2013-0034.24)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Wake Forest; Duke vs. Virginia Tech, January 13, 2013; January 16, 2013 (Box UA2013-0034.25)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Connecticut; Duke vs. Clemson, January 21, 2013; January 24, 2013 (Box UA2013-0034.25)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Boston College; Duke vs. Miami, January 27, 2013; January 31, 2013 (Box UA2013-0034.25)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. North Carolina; Duke vs. Virginia, February 3, 2013; February 8, 2013 (Box UA2013-0034.25)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Maryland; Duke vs. Virginia Tech, February 11, 2013; February 14, 2013 (Box UA2013-0034.25)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Wake Forest; Duke vs. Florida State, February 17, 2013; February 22, 2013 (Box UA2013-0034.25)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Maryland; Duke vs. Miami, February 24, 2013; February 28, 2013 (Box UA2013-0034.25)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. North Carolina; ACC Tournament, March 3, 2013; March 7-10, 2013 (Box UA2013-0034.25)
  - Women's Basketball: NCAA Tournament, March 24, 2013; March 26, 2013 (Box UA2013-0034.25)
  - Women's Basketball: NCAA Norfolk Regionals, 2013 (Box UA2013-0034.25)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. N.C. State, 2013-01-12 (Box UA2013-0034.26)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Georgia Tech, 2013-01-17 (Box UA2013-0034.26)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Miami, 2013-01-23 (Box UA2013-0034.26)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Maryland, 2013-01-26 (Box UA2013-0034.26)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Wake Forest, 2013-01-30 (Box UA2013-0034.26)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Florida State, 2013-02-02 (Box UA2013-0034.26)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. N.C. State, 2013-02-07 (Box UA2013-0034.26)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Boston College, 2013-02-10 (Box UA2013-0034.26)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. North Carolina, 2013-02-13 (Box UA2013-0034.26)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Maryland, 2013-02-16 (Box UA2013-0034.26)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Virginia Tech, 2013-02-21 (Box UA2013-0034.26)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Boston College, 2013-02-24 (Box UA2013-0034.26)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs.Virginia, 2013-02-28 (Box UA2013-0034.26)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Miami, 2013-03-03 (Box UA2013-0034.26)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Virginia Tech, 2013-03-05 (Box UA2013-0034.26)
  - Blue Devil Weekly - Bound, 2007-2008; 2 Volumes (Box UA2013-0034.27)
  - Blue Devil Weekly - Loose Copies, 1996-2001; 2008-2009 (Box UA2013-0034.27)
  - Blue Devil Weekly - Loose Copies, 1993-1996 (Box UA2013-0034.28)
  - Men's Basketball: Banks, Eugene Photos, circa 1990-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.29)
  - Assorted Player Photos, circa 1990-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.29)
  - Men's Basketball: Chris Collins photos, circa 1990-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.29)
  - Assorted Player Photos, circa 1990-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.29)
  - Men's Basketball: Nate James photos, circa 1990-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.29)
  - Football: Photos, circa 1990-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.29)
  - Football: Wallace Wade photos, circa 1990-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.29)
  - Women's Basketball: Clippings, 2012-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.29)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Boston College; Duke vs. Florida State, February 9, 2012; February 12, 2012 (Box UA2013-0034.29)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Miami; Duke vs. North Carolina, February 24, 2012; February 26, 2012 (Box UA2013-0034.29)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Clemson; Duke vs. Connecticut, January 27, 2012; January 30, 2012 (Box UA2013-0034.29)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Virginia Tech; Duke vs. Maryland, February 15, 2012; February 19, 2012 (Box UA2013-0034.29)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Wake Forest; Duke vs. North Carolina, February 2, 2012; February 6, 2012 (Box UA2013-0034.29)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Florida State; Duke vs. Virginia Tech, January 13, 2012; January 15, 2012 (Box UA2013-0034.30)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Georgia Tech; Duke vs. Maryland, January 18, 2012; January 22, 2012 (Box UA2013-0034.30)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. USC Upstate; Duke vs. UNC Wilmington, December 11, 2011; December 20, 2011 (Box UA2013-0034.30)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Temple; Duke vs. Virginia, December 30, 2011; January 2, 2012 (Box UA2013-0034.30)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Wake Forest; Duke vs. NC State, January 6, 2012; January 8, 2012 (Box UA2013-0034.30)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Western Kentucky; Duke vs. Gardner Webb, November 20, 2011; November 25, 2011 (Box UA2013-0034.30)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Pittsburgh; Duke vs. Kentucky, December 4, 2011; December 8, 2011 (Box UA2013-0034.30)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. BYU; Duke vs. Auburn, November 11, 2011; November 18, 2011 (Box UA2013-0034.30)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke vs. Notre Dame; Duke vs. Purdue, November 26, 2011; December 1, 2011 (Box UA2013-0034.30)
  - Women's Basketball: Duke Blue/White; Duke vs. Pfeiffer, October 23, 2011; November 3, 2011 (Box UA2013-0034.30)
  - Women's Basketball: Kathleen Scheer, 2008 (Box UA2013-0034.30)
  - Women's Basketball: NCAA Tournament: Duke vs. St. John's; Duke vs. Stanford, March 24, 2012; March 26, 2012 (Box UA2013-0034.30)
  - GoDuke Website Articles, circa 1990-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.30)
  - Field Hockey: Schedules, 2012 (Box UA2013-0034.30)
  - Jack Williams Oversize Photo, circa 1990-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.30)
  - GoDuke Website Articles, circa 1990-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.30)
  - Lacrosse: Programs, 2002-2003 (Box UA2013-0034.30)
  - Volleyball: Releases, Scores, Stats, 2008; 2 folders (Box UA2013-0034.31)
  - Volleyball: Releases, Scores, Stats, 2007; 2 folders (Box UA2013-0034.31)
  - Fencing: Releases, Scores, Stats, 2007 (Box UA2013-0034.31)
  - Volleyball: Releases, Scores, Stats, 2009; 2 folders (Box UA2013-0034.31)
  - Baseball: Releases, Scores, Stats, 2008; 2 folders (Box UA2013-0034.31)
  - Baseball: Releases, Scores, Stats, 2009; 2 folders (Box UA2013-0034.31)
  - Baseball: Releases, Scores, Stats, 2007; 2 folders (Box UA2013-0034.31)
  - Women's Rowing: Releases, Scores, Stats, 2007-2009 (Box UA2013-0034.31)
  - Football: Clippings, 2010-2011 (Box UA2013-0034.32)
  - Football: Duke vs. Richmond, 2011-09-03 (Box UA2013-0034.32)
    Includes digital disk.
  - Football: Duke vs. Stanford, 2011-09-10 (Box UA2013-0034.32)
  - Football: Duke vs. Boston College, 2011-09-17 (Box UA2013-0034.32)
  - Football: Duke vs. Wake Forest, 2011-10-22 (Box UA2013-0034.32)
  - Football: Duke vs. Tulane, 2011-09-24 (Box UA2013-0034.32)
  - Football: Duke vs. Florida International University, 2011-10-01 (Box UA2013-0034.32)
  - Football: Duke vs. Florida State University, 2011-10-15 (Box UA2013-0034.32)
  - Football: Duke vs. Virginia Tech, 2011-10-29 (Box UA2013-0034.32)
  - Football: Duke vs. University of Miami, 2011-11-05 (Box UA2013-0034.33)
  - Football: Duke vs. University of Virginia, 2011-11-12 (Box UA2013-0034.33)
  - Football: Duke vs. Georgia Tech, 2011-11-19 (Box UA2013-0034.33)
  - Football: Duke vs. North Carolina, 2011-11-26 (Box UA2013-0034.33)
  - Football: Duke vs. Clemson, 2012-11-03 (Box UA2013-0034.33)
  - Football: Duke vs. Georgia Tech, 2012-11-17 (Box UA2013-0034.33)
  - Football: Duke vs. Miami, 2012-11-24 (Box UA2013-0034.33)
  - Football: Composite Sheets: Player Headshots, 1996 (Box UA2013-0034.34)
  - Football: Pictures, 1996 (Box UA2013-0034.34)
  - Football: Slides, 1997 (Box UA2013-0034.34)
  - Football: Pictures, 1997 (Box UA2013-0034.34)
  - Football: Cincinnati vs. Duke, 2012-12-27 (Box UA2013-0034.34)
  - Football: Composite Sheets: Player Headshots, 1995 (Box UA2013-0034.35)
  - Football: Slides, 1995 (Box UA2013-0034.35)
  - Football: Pictures, 1995 (Box UA2013-0034.35)
  - Football: Photos/Slides/Media Guides/Negatives, 1994 (Box UA2013-0034.35)
  - Football: Contact Sheets and Photos, 1993 (Box UA2013-0034.35)
  - Football: Composite, Contact Sheets, and Photos, 1992 (Box UA2013-0034.35)
  - Football: Composite Sheets: Player Headshots, 1991 (Box UA2013-0034.35)
  - Football: Contact Sheets and Photos, 1990 (Box UA2013-0034.35)
  - Football: Team Photos, 1986 (Box UA2013-0034.36)
  - Football: Contact Sheets and Photos, 1989 (Box UA2013-0034.36)
  - Football: Media Guide, 1988 (Box UA2013-0034.36)
  - Football: Media Guide, 2007 (Box UA2013-0034.36)
  - Football: Duke vs. Connecticut, 2007-09-01 (Box UA2013-0034.36)
  - Football: Duke vs. Virginia, 2007-09-08 (Box UA2013-0034.36)
  - Football: Duke vs. Northwestern, 2007-09-15 (Box UA2013-0034.36)
  - Football: Duke vs. Navy, 2007-09-22 (Box UA2013-0034.36)
  - Football: Duke vs. Miami, 2007-09-29 (Box UA2013-0034.36)
  - Football: Duke vs. Wake Forest, 2007-10-06 (Box UA2013-0034.37)
  - Football: Duke vs. Virginia Tech, 2007-10-13 (Box UA2013-0034.37)
  - Football: Duke vs. Florida State, 2007-10-27 (Box UA2013-0034.37)
  - Football: Duke vs. Clemson, 2007-11-03 (Box UA2013-0034.37)
  - Football: Duke vs. Georgia Tech, 2007-11-10 (Box UA2013-0034.37)
  - Football: Duke vs. Notre Dame, 2007-11-17 (Box UA2013-0034.37)
  - Football: Duke vs. Alabama, 2006-10-07 (Box UA2013-0034.38)
  - Football: Duke vs. Virginia, 2006-09-30 (Box UA2013-0034.38)
  - Football: Duke vs. Virginia Tech, 2006-09-16 (Box UA2013-0034.38)
  - Football: Duke vs. Richmond, 2006-09-02 (Box UA2013-0034.38)
  - Football: Duke vs. North Carolina, 2007-11-24 (Box UA2013-0034.38)
  - Football: Spring Game, 2008-04-19 (Box UA2013-0034.38)
  - Football: Duke vs. Wake Forest, 2006-09-09 (Box UA2013-0034.39)
  - Football: Duke vs. Florida State, 2006-10-14 (Box UA2013-0034.39)
  - Football: Duke vs. Miami, 2006-10-21 (Box UA2013-0034.39)
  - Football: Duke vs. Vanderbilt, 2006-10-28 (Box UA2013-0034.39)
  - Football: Duke vs. Navy, 2006-11-04 (Box UA2013-0034.39)
  - Football: Duke vs. Boston College, 2006-11-11 (Box UA2013-0034.39)
  - Football: Duke vs. Georgia Tech, 2006-11-18 (Box UA2013-0034.40)
  - Football: Duke vs. North Carolina, 2006-11-25 (Box UA2013-0034.40)
  - Football: General, 2006 (Box UA2013-0034.40)
  - Football: Yearbook, 2005 (Box UA2013-0034.40)
  - Football: General Football Articles, 2005 (Box UA2013-0034.40)
  - Football: General, 2005-2006 (Box UA2013-0034.40)
  - Football: Duke vs. East Carolina, 2005-09-03 (Box UA2013-0034.40)
  - Football: Duke vs. Virginia Tech, 2005-09-10 (Box UA2013-0034.40)
  - Football: Duke vs. VMI, 2005-09-17 (Box UA2013-0034.41)
  - Football: Duke vs. Virginia, 2005-09-24 (Box UA2013-0034.41)
  - Football: Duke vs. Navy, 2005-10-01 (Box UA2013-0034.41)
  - Football: Duke vs. Miami, 2005-10-08 (Box UA2013-0034.41)
  - Football: Duke vs. Georgia Tech, 2005-10-15 (Box UA2013-0034.41)
  - Football: Duke vs. Florida State, 2005-10-22 (Box UA2013-0034.41)
  - Football: Duke vs. Wake Forest, 2002-10-29 (Box UA2013-0034.41)
  - Football: Duke vs. Clemson, 2005-11-05 (Box UA2013-0034.41)
  - Football: Duke vs. North Carolina, 2005-11-19 (Box UA2013-0034.42)
  - Football: Pictures, 2005 (Box UA2013-0034.42)
  - Football: Recruits, 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.42)
  - Football: Preseason, 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.42)
  - Football: Yearbook, 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.42)
  - Football: Duke vs. Navy, 2004-09-04 (Box UA2013-0034.42)